Town Hall - Zombie
Developed and produced by: Nexon
Texture/Modeling/Edited by: Nexon

During the battle between Terrorists and Counter-Terrorists, strange, undead creatures have emerged from the Rex Laboratory. The humans have no choice but to work together to survive.

Humans: Survive the zombie attacks until time runs out, or kill all the zombies.
Zombies: Kill all the humans and turn them into zombies. Zombies have more HP and are faster than humans.